<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Make Yourself Designs</title>
    <link>http://makeyourselfdesigns.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Make Yourself Designs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 13:14:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://makeyourselfdesigns.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOG 3</title>
      <link>http://makeyourselfdesigns.com/blog/blog-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 13:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://makeyourselfdesigns.com/blog/blog-3/</guid>
      <description>How to travel with beauty products What to use and how to organize beauty products for traveling
Going on vacation or just out of town for the weekend can be so relaxing, although it usually includes a good amount of planning(and some stress!) ahead of time. I bet the last thing you want to worry about on your trip is your makeup and beauty products spilling and leaking in your luggage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Morning Motivation Hacks for Productivity</title>
      <link>http://makeyourselfdesigns.com/blog/5-morning-motivation-hacks-for-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 13:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://makeyourselfdesigns.com/blog/5-morning-motivation-hacks-for-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Time saving ideas and inspiration to get you out of the house quicker and have a happier and ultimately more successful day.
Are you a morning person? Okay good, me neither. Mornings always have a few crazy elements to them, one of them being stress. Stressful mornings can sometimes lead to not so easy days, which then lead to laying on the couch with zero motivation when you get home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Ready in 30 Minutes or Less</title>
      <link>http://makeyourselfdesigns.com/blog/how-to-get-ready-for-work-in-30-minutes-or-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 12:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://makeyourselfdesigns.com/blog/how-to-get-ready-for-work-in-30-minutes-or-less/</guid>
      <description>Getting ready to go out with friends is one of my favorite activities; looking cute, doing my makeup, the whole thing. However, getting ready for work or school? This is one of my least favorite because if you’re like me, you’re constantly checking your clock to make sure you have time for x y and z. If you’re tired of racing out the door, keep reading because I am going to show you some easy things to incorporate into your routine that will help you get ready for work in 30 minutes or less.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>